# MARWAN GRADA

UI Designer / Developer

## **PROFILE**

I am a UX/UI designer with more than 4 years experience. I love creating aesthetically pleasing and functional web products using user-centered design approach. Turning complex problems into a simple beautiful interface.

I round out my technical skills with a unique professional background in business and education, to work at the intersection of human behavior and technology to design products that listen to the users' needs.

## CONTACT

#### PHONE

347-666-4317

### **EMAIL**

grada.luck@gmail.com

## WEBSITE

www.marwangrada.com

## **EXPERIENCE**

2013 - Present

## **UI Designer / Developer**

GIA (Gemological Institute of America)

Web Content Specialist ( Jan 2017 - Present ) SD,CA

Kehecweh

Web Developer / Designer ( Sep 2014 - Present ) Remote

Web Developer / Designer ( Aug 2015 - Sep 2016 ) NYC & Remote

Graphic Designer (Feb 2016 - June 2016 ) NYC & Remote

Katz Media Group

Web Designer ( March 2014 - May 2014 ) NYC & Remote

Story Worldwide

Graphic/Web Designer (Oct 2013 - Aug 2015) NYC & Remote

## **EDUCATION**

2015 - 2016 New York Code + Design Academy

Web Development/ UX Design Certification

2014 - 2016 Touro College NYC

Masters in Education - TESOL

2004 - 2009 **University of Tripoli** 

Bachelors in Business Administration

## SKILLS

HTML5

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS SOFT SKILLS**

fm

Critical thinking Adaptability Javascript (React.js, Node.js, JQuery) Negotiation Photoshop Illustrator Communication Indesign Problem solving Adobe XD **Emotional Intelligence** Wordpress PHP Commitment

SQL Organization